There is a woman there, a young woman, I don't want her to be shy.
It's like your parents forced you to marry a man.
After marrying the man, you have a child with the man.
You are dressed in a native attire.
What is happening now is that your eyes have been opened.
You want to leave the marriage. Please come forward.
You are well-educated. Very beautiful. Every quality - you have it.
You realised that this man is nothing. Now, there is no affection.
You want to leave the marriage. You have an issue. Please come forward.
You are there.
You are there. This issue is very pathetic. I am calling you out, because only Jesus can settle this.
Watch your screen.
I am the person, sir. I was forced to marry a man,
when I was 19 years old. Now, I don't have any affection for him.
I don't even want to see him, now. I want to leave the marriage.
I have a son with him, who is 2 years old.
Why do you want to leave the marriage ?
I don't have affection for him. I don't love him.
At the beginning, how did you people get married ?
I was introduced to him by his sister. I didn't know him before.
What (gender) is the child you have with the man ?
I have a son with him.
A boy. 2 years old.
What do you want to do ? Can't you see that son
is very important to you.
He is very important to me.
You look good, your appearance, what is your secret ?
Do you mean that your man is not financially supporting you?
Or that he's not the secret of you looking good ?
He is a good man. He is taking good care of me.
Anything I ask for, he will give it to me.
My daughter, my sister,
I want to see the man. I want to see your son. I want to see you.
We hold a meeting. You people go through deliverance.
Now, it is the will of God.
Thank you, my Lord. Thank you.
After deliverance you will have that affection you don't have for him.
Everything will be alright.
Thank you, Lord. Thank you, Jesus.
Standard For Life
This is a house that is about to be destroyed, separated, scattered.
The question now is, what God is saying ?
Ok, let the husband and wife come out.
Watch your screen as they are now coming out.
I am just meeting my brother for the first time, now.
My brother,
we are here today to settle your home, and
to make sure that there is peace in your house.
And to hear God's opinion, on what does God say about this issue.
What you have in mind does not matter but what God says.
So lets hear it.
My name is Ufemia Eze.
Here with me is my husband, Bassey Eze.
And my son, Victor Eze.
We are all from Enugu State.
I am here to confirm the prophecy to be perfectly true for my life.
That's the problem which brought me here to the SCOAN.
The man is God said that there was a young woman here.
It's like your parents forced you to marry a certain man.
Now your eyes are opened, you want to leave the marriage.
You have a son for him.
I am here to confirm the prophecy to be perfectly true, because
I prayed and fasted asking God that I wanted to know His opinion about this marriage.
I want to know if this marriage is from God.
I want to know from God, either for me to continue with this marriage
or to divorce.
Last Sunday, God answered my prayer.
It's true. I used to think about leaving this marriage.
The reasons are: he is much older than I am.
He is 17 years older than I am.
When I married him. I didn't know anything about love in a marriage.
Now, I don't have love for him. I don't have affection for him.
Whenever I see him, I have hatred for him.
I don't want to see him at all.
There was a time I told him that I wanted to go and stay on in the village.
So that we would be seeing each other only once in a while.
Because I don't want to see him. Whenever I see him....
I only have hatred for him.
There was a time we stayed 5 good months in the same room.
on the same bed without making love, because the affection was not there.
I do see strange men making love to me in my dream.
I do see dead people in dreams. I even fly in my dream.
Are you ready to listen to the voice of God ?
Yes. That's why I am here.
Who is TB Joshua?
He is man of God.
Before I tell you the voice of God. I want you to be on your knees in front of this man.
You need deliverance.
You just need deliverance.
You have a spiritual husband.
This spiritual husband has married you.
After yours deliverance you would know this is a nice man.
This is the man you need to marry.
Those things you consider... You said he's 17 years older than you are.
You are very lucky to have this man.
Handsome and beauty.
This man would go to work from morning till night and give you the entire amount of money.
You use it to do crayon and pencils.
Look at this handsome man, good looking man.
It's not your fault. Because he told you his age.
You just need deliverance.
Father, thank you Lord.
In Jesus Christ name.
Stand up.
Give your husband a kiss.
Mouth to mouth.
Hallelujah !
It's all about this spiritual husband.
You will start to see the affection now, right as I'm talking now.
You will go to the mountain and thank God.
So, thank you.
I don't want to hear anything from my brother. I am meeting him for the first time.
He only sees the way his wife has been behaving, keeping distance.
She doesn't want a touch, or anything. But he is hearing
this for the first time that his wife wants to leave the marriage.
I need to meet him. And that is the end.
The issue is not the outward beauty, we are talking of the inner one.
This brother is very very handsome on the inside.
While this lady is beautiful on the outside.
The reason why man and woman come together...
When the husband is weak, the wife is strong. When the wife is weak, the husband is strong.
They help each other.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here, to subscribe, to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
Stay up-to-date for the latest prophecies, deliverances, service and testimonies from SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV, changing lives, changing nations, and changing the world.